Question. I'd like to give you a situation and ask you to act it out. You want to invite
another couple to your home for dinner. Ask your family member three or four questions
to find out when the best day and time is to have your friends come for dinner.
Answer.
Honey, do you remember Jamie? If you are okay with it, I was thinking of inviting her couple
over for dinner. What do you think? Great. So what day works best for you? I heard they're
free this Sunday. Would that work for you too? Then what time do you think is good? Is seven
is okay? I think it's a nice time. Not too early, not too late. And oh yeah, what should
we prepare for dinner? If we can't decide right now, I can just ask them what kind of
food they like. Alright, that's all set.